(CAR SKIDDING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ GET BUSY ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S TALKING
ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT ME ♪
♪ WHY DON'T THEY
JUST LET ME LIVE ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED COMMISSION,
MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS ♪
♪ THAT'S MY PREROGATIVE ♪
♪ THEY SAY I'M CRAZY ♪
♪ I REALLY DON'T CARE ♪
♪ THAT'S MY PREROGATIVE ♪
♪ THEY SAY I'M NASTY ♪
♪ BUT I DON'T GIVE A DAMN ♪
♪ GETTING GIRLS IS HOW I LIVE ♪
♪ SOME MESSY QUESTIONS ♪
♪ WHY AM I SO REAL ♪
♪ BUT THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND ME ♪
♪ I REALLY DON'T KNOW THE
DEAL ABOUT HER BROTHER ♪
♪ TRYING HARD TO MAKE IT RIGHT ♪
♪ NOT LONG AGO ♪
♪ BEFORE I WIN
THIS FIGHT, SING ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S TALKING
ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT ME ♪
♪ WHY DON'T THEY
JUST LET ME LIVE ♪
♪ TELL ME WHY I DON'T
NEED COMMISSION ♪
♪ MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS ♪
♪ THAT'S MY PREROGATIVE ♪
♪ IT'S MY PREROGATIVE
(IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ IT'S THE WAY THAT I WANNA
LIVE (IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ I CAN DO JUST WHAT I FEEL
(IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ NO ONE CAN TELL ME WHAT TO
DO (IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WHAT I'M DOING
I'M DOING FOR YOU ♪
♪ DON'T GET ME WRONG ♪
♪ I'M REALLY NOT SOUPED ♪
♪ EGO TRIPS IS NOT MY THING ♪
♪ ALL THESE STRANGE
RELATIONSHIPS REALLY
GETS ME DOWN ♪
♪ I SEE NOTHING WRONG IN
SPREADING MYSELF AROUND, SING ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S TALKING
ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT ME ♪
♪ WHY DON'T THEY
JUST LET ME LIVE ♪
♪ TELL ME WHY I DON'T
NEED COMMISSION ♪
♪ MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS ♪
♪ THAT'S MY PREROGATIVE ♪
♪ IT'S MY PREROGATIVE
(IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ I CAN DO WHAT I WANNA
DO (IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ I CAN LIVE MY LIFE
(IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ AND I'M DOING IT JUST FOR
YOU (IT'S MY PREROGATIVE) ♪
♪ TELL ME, TELL ME WHY
CAN'T I LIVE MY LIFE ♪
♪ LIVE MY LIFE WITHOUT
ALL OF THE THINGS ♪
♪ THAT PEOPLE SAY OH ♪
♪ YO, TEDDY KICK IT LIKE THIS ♪
♪ OH NO NO I CAN DO
WHAT I WANNA DO ♪
♪ ME AND YOU TOGETHER TOGETHER
TOGETHER TOGETHER TOGETHER ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S TALKING
ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT ME ♪
♪ WHY DON'T THEY
JUST LET ME LIVE? ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED COMMISSION ♪
♪ MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS ♪
♪ THAT'S MY PREROGATIVE ♪
♪ EVERYBODY'S TALKING
ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT ME ♪
♪ WHY DON'T THEY
JUST LET ME LIVE? ♪
♪ I DON'T NEED COMMISSION ♪
♪ MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS ♪
♪ THAT'S MY PREROGATIVE ♪
♪ WHAT IS THIS, A BLIZZARD ♪
♪ THAT I CAN'T HAVE MONEY IN
MY POCKET AND PEOPLE NOT
TALK ABOUT ME ♪
♪ THIS WORLD IS A TRIP ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOIN' ON THESE DAYS ♪
♪ GOT THIS PERSON OVER HERE
TALKIN' ABOUT ME, THIS PERSON ♪
♪ AY, LISTEN, LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHIN', IT'S MY PREROGATIVE ♪
♪ I CAN DO WHAT I WANNA DO ♪
♪ I MADE THIS MONEY,
YOU DIDN'T; RIGHT, TED ♪
♪ WE OUTTA HERE ♪
♪ IT'S MY, IT'S MY,
IT'S MY, IT'S MY ♪
♪ IT'S MY, MY, MY, MY, MY, MY,
MY, MY, MY, MY, MY, MY, MY ♪
♪ IT'S MY...WOO ♪
♪ IT'S MY PREROGATIVE, IT'S MY ♪
♪ IT'S MY, IT'S MY, MY, MY ♪
♪ IT'S MY PREROGATIVE,
CAN'T YOU SEE, BABY DOLL ♪
♪ HA, WHY YOU WANNA
TALK ABOUT ME ♪
♪ TELL ME, TELL ME WHY ♪
(CROWD APPLAUDING)